Bum, bum, da-da-da-da-bum, da-da-da-da-bum, da-da-da-da-bum, da-da-da-da-da-da.
What's up, Montgomery, Alabama?
So y'all know how we was hyped and, you know, for the ancestors with the brawl that happened down at the riverfront?
And how the mayor handled that?
We were happy, right?
Did you know that there is a mayor election on August 22nd?
It's okay, I didn't know either.
I see your reaction.
But this is what I need you to do.
If you are registered to vote, you need to take your butt down and vote on August 22nd.
If you are not registered to vote, if you show up with your proof of address and your ID on the day of the election,
they have to register you and they have to give you a ballot for you to vote.
You see how they just be trying to slide shit past us?
Yeah, I ain't going.
Y'all blow this video up so we can make sure that the current mayor of Montgomery stays the current mayor of Montgomery.
And I'm out.